The first phase is hallucinogenic... the second phase is
glandular... and the third phase is... BODY MELT
Body Melt is a comedy, horror, science fiction film directed by Philip Brophy.
Residents of peaceful Pebbles Court, Homesville, are being used unknowingly as test experiments for a new
'Body Drug' that causes rapid body decomposition (melting skin etc.) and painful death.
Det. Sam Phillips, played by Gerard Kennedy.
Johnno, played by Andrew Daddo.
Dr. Carrera, played by Ian Smith.
Shaan, played by Regina Gaigalas.
Pud, played by Vincent Gil.
Bab, played by Neil Foley.
Ben Geurens (born 24 December 1979) is an Australian actor.
The film explores themes of australia, pregnancy,
mutant, transformation, car crash.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.